Oscar Lundberg
☐ +46 709 440 360
☑ jensoscarlundberg95@gmail.com
⑤ jol95.github.io

June 13, 2023

Hello,

I am an enthusiastic and ambitious computer engineering student with a strong passion for development and AI solutions. After studying computer engineering for five years, although I have not yet completed my degree, I have made the decision to start seeking employment rather than continuing my education. Throughout my studies, I have discovered that I truly enjoy the field of development, while finding less enthusiasm for extensive engineering mathematics.

I offer a solid foundation in data studies, having gained knowledge across various areas. I am now eager to transition from being a student to an active participant in the professional world. Engaging in recent major project works has reinforced my belief that working on practical assignments and delving into specific subjects and technologies is incredibly rewarding. I am confident that my academic background has equipped me with the necessary skills to quickly adapt and learn new tools and tasks.

While I may currently lack extensive work experience, I guarantee my utmost motivation, dedication, and a strong work ethic to continuously grow and excel. I welcome any inquiries or questions you may have and eagerly anticipate the opportunity to hear from you.

Thank you for your time and consideration.

Best regards, Oscar Lundberg

Oscar Lundberg

☐ +46 709 440 360
☐ jensoscarlundberg95@gmail.com
ⓒ jol95.github.io
in oscar-lundberg-219094272/

Education

2017-Present Master of Science in Computer Science and Engineering, Luleå Tekniska

Universitet, Luleå

Completed High school program, International baccalaureate Katedralskolan, Skara

2015

Projects

2022 Sep-Jan Web interaction Developer, Luleå Maker Space, Luleå

The project was for an ideal local company wanting to create more interested in programming for young children, especially girls. My work revolved around developing web interactions on a robot, Pepper, to allow users to navigate popular sites such as Google or Wikipedia using voice commands. Most of my works was in Python. But I also worked an AI model, OpenAI's Whisper as a transcription solution.

2019 Oct-Mar Frontend Developer, LTU, Luleå

The project goal was to provide a service a user can simulate their own P2P networks and simulate them. The user case in this case was to simulate data from self driving machines. I worked as a frontend developer using Javascript as well as D3.js to provide a visual simulations using graphs.

Work Experience

2016–2017 Substitute teacher, Valleskolan, Axvall

I worked at the local elementary school. I was mainly assisting teacher, but by the end had some classes of my own with the younger children. As well as being a part of the after school care they provided.

2015-2016 Machine operator, Arla, Götene

Arla is a big company in dairy. Most of my work was at the butter department, were I operated machines. Eventually I was given more responsibility and could manage the people operating for our department

2014 Salesmen, Verisure, Stavanger

Nov-Mar For a couple of months I was in Norway working as a door salesmen selling home alarm systems.

11-12-14 Machine operator, Nolato, Götene

For the summers of 2011, 2012 and 2014 I worked at a plastic factory. Most of the work entailed production and warehouse work.

2013 2014 Swedish teacher, SFI, Skara

During high school I volunteered at SFI (Swedish for immigrants) were I assisted in teaching Swedish.

Computer skills

Basic Java, Anaconda, Unity, JavaScript, Blender

Intermediate REACT, TYPESCRIPT, PYTHON, HTML, LATEX, MICROSOFT OFFICE, LINUX,

WINDOWS, OPENAI PRODUCTS

Languages

Swedish Native language

English Fluent Fluent Fluent in text and speech

Interests

- Artificial Intelligence

- Cooking

- Reading

- Web development
- Weight lifting
- Gaming